（标题嘶嘶作响）
(title whooshes)
（标志弹出）
(logo pops)
（标题嘶嘶作响）
(title whooshes)
- 如何在 Hugging Face 论坛上提问？
- How to ask a question on the Hugging Face forums?
如果你有一般性问题
If you have a general question
或者正在调试你的代码，
or are looking to debug your code,
论坛是提问的地方。
the forums are the place to ask.
在这个视频中，我们将教你
In this video we will teach you
如何写出一个好问题，
how to write a good question,
以最大限度地提高你获得答案的机会。
to maximize the chances you will get an answer.
首先，登录论坛，
First things first, to login on the forums,
你需要一个 Hugging Face 帐户。
you need a Hugging Face account.
如果你还没有创建一个，
If you haven't created one already,
转到 hf.co 并单击注册。
go to hf.co and click sign up.
下面还有一个直接链接。
There is also a direct link below.
填写你的邮箱和密码，
Fill your email and password,
然后继续选择你的用户名的步骤
then continue the steps to pick your username
并更新头像。
and update a profile picture.
完成后，去 discuss.huggingface.co，
Once this is done, go to discuss.huggingface.co,
下方链接，点击登录。
link below, and click log in.
使用与以下相同的登录信息
Use the same login information as
Hugging Face 网站。
for the Hugging Face website.
你可以通过单击搜索论坛
You can search the forums by clicking
在放大镜上。
on the magnifying glass.
可能有人已经在某个主题中问过你的问题。
Someone may have already asked your question in a topic.
如果你发现你无法作为新用户发布新主题，
If you find you can't post a new topic as a new user,
这可能是因为反垃圾邮件过滤器。
it may be because of the antispam filters.
确保你花一些时间阅读现有主题
Make sure you spend some time reading existing topics
停用它。
to deactivate it.
当你确定你的问题还没有被问到时，
When you're sure your question hasn't been asked yet,
单击新主题按钮。
click on the new topic button.
对于此示例，我们将使用以下代码，
For this example, we'll use the following code,
产生错误，
that produces an error,
正如我们在 “遇到错误时该怎么办” 视频中看到的那样。
as we saw in the "What to do when I get an error" video.
第一步是为我们的新主题选择一个类别。
The first step is to pick a category for our new topic.
由于我们的错误与 Transformers 库有关，
Since our error has to do with the Transformers library,
我们选择这个类别。
we pick this category.
接下来，选择一个能够很好地总结你的错误的标题。
Next, choose a title that summarizes your error well.
不要太含糊，否则用户会遇到与你相同的错误
Don't be too vague or users that get the same error you did
以后将无法找到你的主题。
in the future won't be able to find your topic.
输入完主题标题后，
Once you have finished typing your topic title,
确保问题没有得到回答
make sure the question hasn't been answered
在 Discourse 主题中建议你。
in the topics Discourse suggests you.
单击十字删除该窗口
Click on the cross to remove that window
当你仔细检查时。
when you have double-checked.
这是发布错误时不应执行的操作的示例。
This is an example of what not to do when posting an error.
消息非常模糊，
The message is very vague,
所以没有人能猜出哪里出了问题
so no one else will be able to guess what went wrong
对你来说，它标记了太多人。
for you, and it tags too many people.
标记人，尤其是版主，
Tagging people, especially moderators,
可能会产生与你想要的相反的效果。
might have the opposite effect of what you want.
当你向他们发送通知时，他们会收到很多通知，
As you send them a notification, and they get plenty,
他们可能不会费心回复你，
they will probably not bother replying to you,
而你没有标记的用户可能会忽略这些问题，
and users you didn't tag will probably ignore the questions,
因为他们看到被标记的用户。
since they see tagged users.
仅在你完全确定时才标记用户
Only tag a user when you are completely certain
他们是回答你问题的最佳场所。
they are the best place to answer your question.
文本要准确，如果出现错误
Be precise in your text, and if you have an error coming
从一段特定的代码，包括该代码
from a specific piece of code, include that code
在你的帖子中。
in your post.
为了确保你的帖子看起来不错，请提出你的问题
To make sure your post looks good, place your question
在像这样的三个反引号之间。
between three backticks like this.
你可以在右边查看
You can check on the right
发布后你的帖子将如何显示。
how your post will appear once posted.
如果你的问题是关于错误的，
If your question is about an error,
最好包括完整的回溯。
it's even better to include the full traceback.
正如 “遇到错误时该怎么办” 视频中所述，
As explained in the "What to do when I get an error" video,
如果你使用的是 Colab，请展开回溯。
expand the traceback if you're on Colab.
就像代码一样，把它
Like for the code, put it
在包含三个反引号的两行之间
between two lines containing three backticks
正确格式化。
for proper formatting.
我们最后的建议是记住要友善。
Our last advice is to remember to be nice.
一句 “请” 和一句 “谢谢” 将大有帮助
A "Please," and a "Thank you" will go a long way
让别人帮助你。
into getting others to help you.
一切都做好后，
With all that done properly,
你的问题应该很快就会得到答案。
your question should get an answer pretty quickly.
（标题嘶嘶作响）
(title whooshes)
（标题失败）
(title fizzles)